proxy-list.download 2019-08-28

# Privacy Policy - Proxy-List.Download

The protection of your privacy is very important to us, in this page we provide our privacy policy notice explaining the way your personal information is collected and used.

Our website track basic information about our visitors / users to improve the usage of the site, and to collect traffic statistics.

By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

## Log Data

We want to inform you that whenever you visit our website, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data.

These could include, but are not limited to:

• Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.

• Browser type, version, plug-in details.

• Local time zone.

• Pages of our Site that you visit.

• Date and time of each request (i.e. arrival, the time spent and exit on each page).

• Language preference.

• Referring site.

• Device type (i.e. desktop, laptop, or smartphone).

• Screen size, screen color depth, and system fonts.

• And other statistics.

### Cloudflare

On this website, we use the service Cloudflare to provide security against DDoS attacks, identify trusted web traffic and improve site performance through CDN (Content Distribution Network). Further information about Clouflare’s Privacy Policy may be obtained from <https://www.cloudflare.com/privacyshield/>. 

### Google Analytics

On this website, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. This service allow us to collect information about your use of our website. All collected information will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, provide reports of the site visitors and other services relating to website activity and usage. Further information about Google’s Privacy Policy may be obtained from <https://policies.google.com/privacy>. 

## Cookies

We use our own and third-party cookies to optimize your browsing and service experience on our website. Remember that you can reject them or change their configuration on your browser , but keep in mind that access, use and, in general, navigation through our website means the user's consent to the use of cookies by us / or our third-party service providers.

You can obtain extended information about cookies and their use here [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

### Types of cookies we use.

**• Navigation Cookies:** These cookies collect information about user activitys, for example, page views, navigation, loading errors ... It is generic and anonymous information, where personal data are not included, It's mainly used to optimize your browsing and service experience on our website.

**• Advertising Cookies:** These allow us / or third-parties to manage advertising spaces that could be shown on our website, adapting the content of the advertisement to the content you are looking for. We can analyze your browsing habits on the Internet and we can show you advertisements related to your browsing profile.

However, since cookies are not strictly necessary to use our website, we remind you that you can allow, block or delete them through your browser settings.

## Contact Form

In order to use our [Contact Form](https://www.proxy-list.download/Contact), you must enter the minimum information necessary to answer your message: Your name and your email. These data that you provide will be used only to respond to your message, it will be used confidentially and never will be stored, disclosed or shared with third parties. 

#### We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify to all visitors by placing a prominent notice at our home page.
